Edwin Way Teale Papers 1981.0009
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series XIII: Photographs, undated, 1860s-1990s
  - Subseries A: Negatives, 1912-1978
    - 3 1/4" x 4 1/4" Negatives
      - Bat Experiments, 1940 November 20 (Box 267:, Folder 1132-1133)
      - Bodog F. Beck (Bee Therapy), 1940 December 10 (Box 267:, Folder 1134)
      - Dragonfly Nymph (Staten Island Museum), 1940 December 16 (Box 267:, Folder 1135)
      - Lacewing Eggs, 1940 December 29 (Box 267:, Folder 1136)
      - Five Leading Hobbies, 1941 January 4 (Box 267:, Folder 1137-1140)
      - Kodachrome of Rutland, VT, 1941 February 20 (Box 267:, Folder 1141)
      - Polarizing Instrument Company, 1941 February 21 (Box 267:, Folder 1142)
      - Making a Coil Condenser, 1941 February 25 (Box 267:, Folder 1143)
      - Princeton Listening Center, 1941 March 19 (Box 267:, Folder 1144-1145)
      - Carpenter Bee Tunnels, 1941 March 20 (Box 267:, Folder 1146)
      - Eyespots on Wings (Lepidoptera), 1941 March 29 (Box 267:, Folder 1147)
      - Eyespots on Wings, 1941 March 29 (Box 267:, Folder 1148)
      - "W" in Wing of 17-Year Cicada, 1941 March 30 (Box 267:, Folder 1149)
      - Small Shops in the War, 1941 April 2 (Box 267:, Folder 1150-1151)
      - Face of Rat-Tailed Maggot Fly, 1941 April 18 (Box 267:, Folder 1152)
      - The Victors, 1941 April 20 (Box 267:, Folder 1153)
      - Bee-Fly on Phlox Sublata, 1941 April 27 (Box 267:, Folder 1154)
      - Bagworm Bogs, 1941 April 27 (Box 267:, Folder 1155)
      - Queen Bumblebee, 1941 April 27 (Box 267:, Folder 1156)
      - Yellow Butterfly, 1941 April 30 (Box 267:, Folder 1157)
      - W.M.T. Davis in His Laboratory, 1941 April 18 (Box 267:, Folder 1158)
      - Wasp Nest, 1941 April 30 (Box 267:, Folder 1159-1160)
      - Fly on Grape Leaf, 1941 May 10 (Box 267:, Folder 1161)
      - Jumping Spider in Dandelion Head, 1941 May 17 (Box 267:, Folder 1162)
      - Dandelion, 1941 May 17 (Box 267:, Folder 1163)
      - Polistes Wasp, 1941 May 17 (Box 267:, Folder 1164)
      - White Pines, 1941 May 20 (Box 267:, Folder 1165)
      - Damselfly (on Wild Iris), 1941 May 24 (Box 267:, Folder 1166-1167)
      - Lacewing on Iris, 1941 May 24 (Box 267:, Folder 1168)
      - Vincent Shaefer, 1941 May 27 (Box 267:, Folder 1169)
      - Aphis with Ball on Antennae, 1941 May 30 (Box 267:, Folder 1170)
      - Close up of Aphines, 1941 June 8 (Box 267:, Folder 1171)
      - Grass-Sucking Bug, 1941 June 8 (Box 267:, Folder 1172)
      - Ward's Natural History Establishment, 1941 June 12 (Box 267:, Folder 1173)
      - Dragonfly Close up, 1941 June 20 (Box 267:, Folder 1174)
      - Wasp at Garden, 1941 June 20 (Box 267:, Folder 1175)
      - Goldenrod Gall Cut Open, 1941 June 20 (Box 267:, Folder 1176)
      - Leopard Moth, 1941 June 20 (Box 267:, Folder 1177)
      - Fly on Spirea, 1941 June 21 (Box 267:, Folder 1178)
      - Baby Mantis on Baby Grapes, 1941 June 21 (Box 267:, Folder 1179)
      - Froghopper (Backlighting), 1941 June 21 (Box 267:, Folder 1180)
      - Froghopper (Covered with Bubbles), 1941 June 21 (Box 267:, Folder 1181)
      - Froghopper (Second Frog), 1941 June 21 (Box 267:, Folder 1182)
      - Baby Mantis, 1941 June 21 (Box 267:, Folder 1183)
      - Froghopper (Starting Nest), 1941 June 21 (Box 267:, Folder 1184)
      - Froghopper (Tail Lashing), 1941 June 21 (Box 267:, Folder 1185)
      - Froghopper (Making Nest), 1941 June 21 (Box 267:, Folder 1186)
      - Froghopper (Starting Nest), 1941 June 21 (Box 267:, Folder 1187)
      - Baby Mantis on Silk Tassel, 1941 June 21 (Box 267:, Folder 1188)
      - Bumblebee on Foxglove, 1941 June 22 (Box 267:, Folder 1189)
      - Carrion Beetle, 1941 June 22 (Box 267:, Folder 1190)
      - Milkweed Flower, 1941 June 26 (Box 267:, Folder 1191-1192)
      - Froghopper (Close up of Tail), 1941 June 28 (Box 267:, Folder 1193)
      - Froghopper (Legs-Start), 1941 June 28 (Box 267:, Folder 1194)
      - Froghopper (Flies Stuck to Froth), 1941 June 28 (Box 267:, Folder 1195)
      - Froghopper (Middle of Nest Building), 1941 June 28 (Box 267:, Folder 1196)
      - Polistes Wasp (Face of Grub), 1941 July 5 (Box 267:, Folder 1197)
      - Polistes Wasp (Grub), 1941 July 5 (Box 267:, Folder 1198)
      - Polistes Wasp Nest, 1941 July 5 (Box 267:, Folder 1199)
      - Scorpion Fly, 1941 July 5 (Box 267:, Folder 1200)
      - Red Admiral on Hollyhock, 1941 July 5 (Box 267:, Folder 1201)
      - Close up of Wasp Nest, 1941 July 5 (Box 267:, Folder 1202)
      - Lacewing Head, 1941 July 5 (Box 267:, Folder 1203)
      - Polistes Wasp Nest and Me, 1941 July 6 (Box 267:, Folder 1204)
      - Polistes Wasp, 1941 July 6 (Box 267:, Folder 1205)
      - Froghopper (Wing Pads), 1941 July 6 (Box 267:, Folder 1206)
      - Face of Ichneumon Fly, 1941 July 6 (Box 267:, Folder 1207)
      - Ichneumon Fly, 1941 July 6 (Box 267:, Folder 1208)
      - Face of Red Admiral, 1941 July 6 (Box 267:, Folder 1209)
      - Red Admiral on Hollyhock, 1941 July 6 (Box 267:, Folder 1210-1213)
      - Plume Moth on Yarrow, 1941 July 10 (Box 267:, Folder 1214)
      - Froghopper (Making Nest), 1941 July 12 (Box 267:, Folder 1215-1220)
      - Froghopper (Nest Almost Done), 1941 July 12 (Box 267:, Folder 1221)
      - Froghopper (Making Nest), 1941 July 12 (Box 267:, Folder 1222)
      - Amber Wing Dragonfly, 1941 July 12 (Box 267:, Folder 1223)
      - Face of Fly, 1941 July 12 (Box 267:, Folder 1224)
      - Japanese Beetle, 1941 July 12 (Box 267:, Folder 1225)
      - Bug Like Stink Bug, 1941 July 12 (Box 267:, Folder 1226)
      - Leafhopper Like Thorn, 1941 July 12 (Box 267:, Folder 1227)
      - Monarch on Mallow, 1941 August 2 (Box 267:, Folder 1228-1230)
      - Japanese Beetles on Mallow, 1941 August 2 (Box 267:, Folder 1231)
      - Carpenter Bee, 1941 August 2 (Box 267:, Folder 1232)
      - Ambush Bug, 1941 August 6 (Box 267:, Folder 1233)
      - Ant Lion, 1941 August 6 (Box 267:, Folder 1234)
      - Repairing Falcon Feather, 1941 August 6 (Box 267:, Folder 1235)
      - Ant Lion Series, 1941 August 6 (Box 267:, Folder 1236)
      - Ant Lion, 1941 August 6 (Box 267:, Folder 1237)
      - Falcon on Perch, 1941 August 6 (Box 267:, Folder 1238)
      - Duck Hawk, 1941 August 6 (Box 267:, Folder 1239)
      - Falcon Series, 1941 August 6 (Box 267:, Folder 1240)
      - White Butterfly, 1941 August 8 (Box 267:, Folder 1241)
      - Army Pigeons, 1941 August 8 (Box 267:, Folder 1242)
      - Geometrid Larva Camouflaged, 1941 August 8 (Box 267:, Folder 1243)
      - Ambush Bug, 1941 August 9 (Box 267:, Folder 1244)
      - Leaf-Cutter Bee, 1941 August 9 (Box 267:, Folder 1245)
      - Bean Beetle Larva, 1941 August 10 (Box 267:, Folder 1246)
      - Bean Beetle, 1941 August 10 (Box 267:, Folder 1247)
      - Baby Katydid, 1941 August 10 (Box 267:, Folder 1248)
      - Polistes Wasp Nest, 1941 August 10 (Box 267:, Folder 1249)
      - Mourning Cloak, 1941 August 17 (Box 267:, Folder 1250)
      - Ant Lion Series, 1941 August 20 (Box 267:, Folder 1251)
      - Face of Mourning Cloak, 1941 August 24 (Box 267:, Folder 1252)
      - Ant Lion, 1941 August 24 (Box 267:, Folder 1253)
      - Mourning Cloak (Wings Spread), 1941 August 24 (Box 267:, Folder 1254)
      - Mourning Cloak (Side View), 1941 August 24 (Box 267:, Folder 1255)
      - Face of Patter Wasp, 1941 August 24 (Box 267:, Folder 1256)
      - Face of Digger Wasp, 1941 August 30 (Box 267:, Folder 1257)
      - Crab Spider, 1941 August 31 (Box 267:, Folder 1258)
      - Lacewing (Silhouette), 1941 August 31 (Box 267:, Folder 1259)
      - Lacewing (on Wild Lettuce), 1941 August 31 (Box 267:, Folder 1260)
      - Crab Spider, 1941 August 31 (Box 267:, Folder 1261)
      - Polistes Wasp (Face of Male), 1941 August 31 (Box 267:, Folder 1262)
      - Crab Spider and Honeybee, 1941 August 31 (Box 267:, Folder 1263)
      - Snowy Tree Cricket, 1941 September 1 (Box 267:, Folder 1264)
      - Tree Cricket, 1941 September 1 (Box 267:, Folder 1265)
      - Polistes Wasp (Nest), 1941 September 6 (Box 268:, Folder 1266)
      - Monarch (Close up of Wing), 1941 September 6 (Box 268:, Folder 1267)
      - Polistes Wasp (Nest), 1941 September 7 (Box 268:, Folder 1268)
      - Boy's Life Series on Insect Collecting, 1941 September 7 (Box 268:, Folder 1269)
      - Dragonfly, 1941 September 8 (Box 268:, Folder 1270)
      - Mantis Etiquette (How to Feed), 1941 September 27 (Box 268:, Folder 1271)
      - Red Dragonfly on Hollyhock, 1941 September 30 (Box 268:, Folder 1272)
      - Moth From Cocoon at Garden, 1941 September 30 (Box 268:, Folder 1273)
      - Pet Mantis, 1941 October 1 (Box 268:, Folder 1274)
      - Copy of Portrait of W.M.T Davis, 1941 October 4 (Box 268:, Folder 1275)
      - Boy's Life Insect Collecting Series, 1941 October 4 (Box 268:, Folder 1276-1279)
      - Knothole Camera, 1941 October 10 (Box 268:, Folder 1280)
      - Leftovers from Near Horizon, 1941 October 10 (Box 268:, Folder 1281)
      - Cicada Skin, 1941 October 20 (Box 268:, Folder 1282)
      - Yellow Jackets on Apples, 1941 October 20 (Box 268:, Folder 1283)
      - Mantis Eating Its Own Leg, 1941 October 21 (Box 268:, Folder 1284)
      - Red Dragonfly on Milkweed, 1941 October 25 (Box 268:, Folder 1285)
      - Mantis (Silhouette on Milkweed), 1941 October 25 (Box 268:, Folder 1286)
      - Moss at Insect Garden, 1941 October 28 (Box 268:, Folder 1287)
      - Dave Randolph Series, 1941 October 30 (Box 268:, Folder 1288)
      - Warren Roach Series, 1941 November 5 (Box 268:, Folder 1289)
      - Scale Insects on Sumac, 1941 November 15 (Box 268:, Folder 1290)
      - Wooly Aphides, 1941 November 15 (Box 268:, Folder 1291)
      - Ant Lion Pupa Case, 1941 November 22 (Box 268:, Folder 1292)
      - Ant Lion (Close up), 1941 November 22 (Box 268:, Folder 1293-1294)
      - Milkweed Fluff, 1941 November 22 (Box 268:, Folder 1295)
      - Ant Lion (Odds), 1941 November 22 (Box 268:, Folder 1296)
      - Ant Lion Pupa Case, 1941 November 22 (Box 268:, Folder 1297)
      - Polistes Wasp (Last Survivor), 1941 November 22 (Box 268:, Folder 1298)
      - Ant Lion (Going in Ground), 1941 November 30 (Box 268:, Folder 1299)
      - Ant Lion (Top and on Back), 1941 November 30 (Box 268:, Folder 1300)
      - Dave Randolph (Racing) (Pearl Harbor Day), 1941 December 7 (Box 268:, Folder 1301)
      - Ant Lion (Pupa Case), 1941 December 28 (Box 268:, Folder 1302)
      - Roger Troy Peterson Audubon Story, 1942 (Box 268:, Folder 1303-1304)
      - Photomicrograph (Paw of Raccoon in Halftone), 1942 January 6 (Box 268:, Folder 1305)
      - Trilobite (Jay T. Fox), 1942 January 18 (Box 268:, Folder 1306)
      - Fossil Fish (J.T. Fox Museum), 1942 January 18 (Box 268:, Folder 1307)
      - Polyphemus Moth, 1942 February 1 (Box 268:, Folder 1308)
      - Foster Guns, 1942 February 14 (Box 268:, Folder 1309-1311)
      - Christian F. Groth, 1942 March 4 (Box 268:, Folder 1312)
      - Ant Lion, 1942 March 4 (Box 268:, Folder 1313)
      - Foster Revolvers, 1942 March 21 (Box 268:, Folder 1314-1318)
      - Ant Lion (Pattern in Sand), 1942 April 22 (Box 268:, Folder 1319)
      - Mantis Egg Cases (Oddity Cases), 1942 April 22 (Box 268:, Folder 1320)
      - Face of Rat-Tailed Maggot Fly, 1942 April 22 (Box 268:, Folder 1321)
      - Ant Lion (On Back), 1942 April 22 (Box 268:, Folder 1322)
      - New Ants Pouring Out on Grass Blades, 1942 April 22 (Box 268:, Folder 1323)
      - Face of Dunes, 1942 April 22 (Box 268:, Folder 1324)
      - Baby Green Grasshopper on Moss, 1942 April 22 (Box 268:, Folder 1325)
      - Ant Lion (Skin of Adult), 1942 April 22 (Box 268:, Folder 1326)
      - Roots of Sweet Flog, 1942 May 1 (Box 268:, Folder 1327)
      - Anglewing on Apple Blossom, 1942 May 10 (Box 268:, Folder 1328)
      - Grasshopper on Mullein, 1942 May 10 (Box 268:, Folder 1329)
      - Grasshopper on Fluffy Dandelion, 1942 May 10 (Box 268:, Folder 1330)
      - Leech on Mud Turtle, 1942 May 10 (Box 268:, Folder 1331)
      - Mourning Cloak (on Dandelion), 1942 May 10 (Box 268:, Folder 1332)
      - Butterfly on Fiddlehead Fern, 1942 May 10 (Box 268:, Folder 1333)
      - Grasshopper on Grapevine, 1942 May 10 (Box 268:, Folder 1334)
      - Bumblebee on Moss, 1942 May 10 (Box 268:, Folder 1335)
      - Little Butterfly on Grapevine, 1942 May 10 (Box 268:, Folder 1336)
      - Beetle Face from Collection, 1942 May 17 (Box 268:, Folder 1337)
      - Bee Fly Face, 1942 May 17 (Box 268:, Folder 1338)
      - Buffalo Leaf Hopper Face, 1942 May 17 (Box 268:, Folder 1339)
      - The Victors, 1942 May 17 (Box 268:, Folder 1340)
      - Loyalsock Game Farm, 1942 May 27 (Box 268:, Folder 1341-1342)
      - Hawks - Harrisburg Zoo, 1942 May 28 (Box 268:, Folder 1343)
      - Rabbit's Nest, 1942 May 28 (Box 268:, Folder 1344-1345)
      - Chipping Sparrows, 1942 May 28 (Box 268:, Folder 1346)
      - Pheasants Hatching (Loyalsock Game Farm), 1942 May 28 (Box 268:, Folder 1347-1348)
      - Loyalsock Game Farm (Odds), 1942 May 28 (Box 268:, Folder 1349)
      - Owls (Harrisburg Zoo), 1942 June 3 (Box 268:, Folder 1350)
      - Lacewing, 1942 June 6 (Box 268:, Folder 1351)
      - Damselfly on Asparagus, 1942 June 6 (Box 268:, Folder 1352)
      - Dewey Aphides, 1942 June 6 (Box 268:, Folder 1353)
      - Ant Lion, 1942 June 6 (Box 268:, Folder 1354)
      - Iris and Lacewing, 1942 June 6 (Box 268:, Folder 1355)
      - Lacewing (On Feathery Grass), 1942 June 6 (Box 268:, Folder 1356)
      - Lacewing on Iris, 1942 June 6 (Box 268:, Folder 1357)
      - Lacewing and Aphis on Rosebud, 1942 June 6 (Box 268:, Folder 1358)
      - Damselfly on Asparagus, 1942 June 6 (Box 268:, Folder 1359)
      - Damselfly (on Poppy), 1942 June 6 (Box 268:, Folder 1360)
      - Rat-Tailed Maggot, 1942 June 6 (Box 268:, Folder 1361)
      - Damselfly on Feathery Grass, 1942 June 6 (Box 268:, Folder 1362)
      - Damselfly on Poppy Center, 1942 June 6 (Box 268:, Folder 1363)
      - Aphis Wolf and Aphides, 1942 June 6 (Box 268:, Folder 1364)
      - Lacewing (Center of Poppy), 1942 June 6 (Box 268:, Folder 1365)
      - Lacewing on Snake Skin, 1942 June 7 (Box 268:, Folder 1366)
      - Aphid Close up, 1942 June 7 (Box 268:, Folder 1367)
      - Me Among Sweet Flogs, 1942 June 7 (Box 268:, Folder 1368)
      - Bear Mountain Animals, 1942 June 8 (Box 268:, Folder 1369)
      - Salamanders at Bear Mountain, 1942 June 8 (Box 268:, Folder 1370)
      - Animals at Bear Mountain, 1942 June 8 (Box 268:, Folder 1371)
      - Nina Thomas (Teaching Bear Club to Eat), 1942 June 8 (Box 268:, Folder 1372)
      - Nina Thomas (Bear Mountain), 1942 June 8 (Box 268:, Folder 1373)
      - Bear Cub (at Bear Mountain), 1942 June 8 (Box 268:, Folder 1374)
      - Opossum (at Bear Mountain), 1942 June 8 (Box 268:, Folder 1375)
      - Face of Blue-Bodied Dragonfly, 1942 June 20 (Box 268:, Folder 1376)
      - Leaf-Cutter Bee, 1942 June 20 (Box 268:, Folder 1377)
      - "Bumblebee" Robber Fly and Prey, 1942 June 20 (Box 268:, Folder 1378)
      - Knothole Camera (with Rat-Tailed Maggots), 1942 June 25 (Box 268:, Folder 1379)
      - Mr. Davis (at the Garden), 1942 June 25 (Box 268:, Folder 1380)
      - June Beetle, 1942 June 26 (Box 268:, Folder 1381-1382)
      - Face of Bumblebee Robber Fly, 1942 July 6 (Box 268:, Folder 1383)
      - Untitled, 1942 July 20 (Box 268:, Folder 1384)
      - Red Ants Swarming at Insect Garden, 1942 July 20 (Box 268:, Folder 1385)
      - Knothole Camera, 1942 July 22 (Box 268:, Folder 1386)
      - Young Katydid (on Sunflower), 1942 July 24 (Box 268:, Folder 1387)
      - Chlorion Wasp, 1942 July 24 (Box 268:, Folder 1388)
      - Young Katydid (on Sunflower), 1942 July 24 (Box 268:, Folder 1389)
      - Chlorion Wasp, 1942 July 24 (Box 268:, Folder 1390-1391)
      - Victory Flowers, 1942 July 25 (Box 268:, Folder 1392)
      - Locust on Wild Beans, 1942 July 26 (Box 268:, Folder 1393)
      - Damselfly on Wild Bean, 1942 July 26 (Box 268:, Folder 1394)
      - Damselfly on Yarrow, 1942 July 26 (Box 268:, Folder 1395)
      - Lace bugs, 1942 July 26 (Box 268:, Folder 1396)
      - Bulletin Board in Study (Near Horizon), 1942 August 8 (Box 268:, Folder 1397)
      - Me in Study Finishing Near Horizon, 1942 August 8 (Box 268:, Folder 1398)
      - Ants Feeding Honeydew, 1942 August 10 (Box 268:, Folder 1399)
      - Victory Flowers, 1942 August 11 (Box 268:, Folder 1400-1401)
      - Victory Flowers, 1942 August 20 (Box 268:, Folder 1402-1403)
      - Silver Sleeping Upside Down by Curb, 1942 August 24 (Box 268:, Folder 1404)
      - Whelk, 1942 September 6 (Box 268:, Folder 1405)
      - Glass Eyes (Gustou Stoepfer), 1942 September 23 (Box 268:, Folder 1406-1408)
      - Roger T. Peterson (Audubon Story), 1942 September 26 (Box 268:, Folder 1409-1410)
      - Louis Paul Jones, 1942 September 26 (Box 268:, Folder 1411-1413)
      - Mantis Eating Shrew, 1942 October 15 (Box 268:, Folder 1414)
      - Mites on Beetle, 1942 October 24 (Box 269:, Folder 1415)
      - Peterson Pictures (Audubon Features), 1942 October 26 (Box 269:, Folder 1416)
      - Malcolm Rix Pictures (Audubon Features), 1942 October 28 (Box 269:, Folder 1417)
      - Hobart V. Roberts (Outdoor Life Story), 1942 October 29 (Box 269:, Folder 1418)
      - E.L. Palmer Course (Outdoor Life), 1942 October 30 (Box 269:, Folder 1419-1422)
      - Tin Can Stove, 1942 October 31 (Box 269:, Folder 1423)
      - E.L. Palmer (Audubon Story), 1942 October 31 (Box 269:, Folder 1424)
      - Lost Fuertes Sketches, 1942 October 31 (Box 269:, Folder 1425)
      - Cline McKay (Trout Vitamins), 1942 November 2 (Box 269:, Folder 1426)
      - Arthur A. Allen (Audubon Story), 1942 November 2 (Box 269:, Folder 1427)
      - Arthur A. Allen, 1942 November 2 (Box 269:, Folder 1428)
      - George M. Sutton, 1942 November 2 (Box 269:, Folder 1429)
      - Ellsworth Jaeger (Outdoor Living Course), 1942 November 3 (Box 269:, Folder 1430)
      - Bayberries, 1942 November 15 (Box 269:, Folder 1431)
      - Cedar Berries, 1942 November 15 (Box 269:, Folder 1432)
      - Sumac Berries, 1942 November 15 (Box 269:, Folder 1433)
      - N.Y. Times - Near Horizon Reviews, 1942 November 30 (Box 269:, Folder 1434)
      - Silver Cat Asleep Under Xmas Tree, 1942 December 27 (Box 269:, Folder 1435)
      - Preston Jennings (Dry Flies), 1943 February 14 (Box 269:, Folder 1436)
      - David's Youth Fellowship, 1943 March 20 (Box 269:, Folder 1437)
      - The Victors Class, 1943 May 2 (Box 269:, Folder 1438)
      - John Burroughs Medal, 1943 May 20 (Box 269:, Folder 1439)
      - Mantis (Close up of Hatching), 1943 June 9 (Box 269:, Folder 1440)
      - Close up of Polyphemus Moth, 1943 June 9 (Box 269:, Folder 1441)
      - Tent Caterpillars (Diseased), 1943 June 9 (Box 269:, Folder 1442)
      - Sweet Flog (Flower), 1943 June 9 (Box 269:, Folder 1443)
      - Mantis on Egg Case, 1943 June 17 (Box 269:, Folder 1444)
      - David in Cap and Gown, 1943 June 27 (Box 269:, Folder 1445)
      - Insects from Eggs with Spikes Around Top, 1943 July 28 (Box 269:, Folder 1446)
      - Eggs of Lacewing on Rose Twig, 1943 July 28 (Box 269:, Folder 1447)
      - Froghopper (Adult), 1943 July 28 (Box 269:, Folder 1448)
      - Mantis (with Shed Skin), 1943 July 28 (Box 269:, Folder 1449)
      - Lacewing Egg, 1943 July 28 (Box 269:, Folder 1450)
      - Philip Medicus (Military Gun Collection), 1943 August 5 (Box 269:, Folder 1451)
      - Medicus (Military Gun Collection), 1943 August 5 (Box 269:, Folder 1452-1456)
      - Mr. Davis at Garden, 1943 August 20 (Box 269:, Folder 1457)
      - Slug Caterpillar, 1943 August 20 (Box 269:, Folder 1458)
      - Insect Brownie, 1943 August 20 (Box 269:, Folder 1459)
      - Woolly Bear, 1943 August 20 (Box 269:, Folder 1460)
      - Ness (Knife Thrower), 1943 August 29 (Box 269:, Folder 1461-1463)
      - Pinkish Eggs on Leaf, 1943 September 8 (Box 269:, Folder 1464)
      - Putnam Valley School Sanctuary, 1943 September 16 (Box 269:, Folder 1465-1467)
      - Richard Beavers (Kodachromes), 1943 September 8 (Box 269:, Folder 1468)
      - Victory Flowers, 1943 August 20 (Box 269:, Folder 1469)
      - Richard Beavers, 1943 September 19 (Box 269:, Folder 1470-1471)
      - Dune Boy - Marmalade, 1943 October 1 (Box 269:, Folder 1472)
      - Army Equipment, 1943 October 13 (Box 269:, Folder 1473-1475)
      - Sweet Flog, 1943 October 23 (Box 269:, Folder 1476)
      - Medicius - Knives, 1943 November 10 (Box 269:, Folder 1477-1484)
      - Medicius - Guns, 1943 November 10 (Box 269:, Folder 1485-1489)
      - Buckholtz Moth with Plumes, 1944 February 9 (Box 269:, Folder 1490)
      - Joliet "Woodland" School Class, 1944 February 9 (Box 269:, Folder 1491)
      - American Cockroach, 1944 February 9 (Box 269:, Folder 1492)
      - Faces of Insects, 1944 March 24 (Box 269:, Folder 1493)
      - Hibernating Polistes Queen, 1944 March 30 (Box 269:, Folder 1494)
      - Eggs of Clothes Moth on Tie, 1944 March 31 (Box 269:, Folder 1495)
      - The Victors Class, 1944 April 2 (Box 269:, Folder 1496)
      - Insect Faces, 1944 April 10 (Box 269:, Folder 1497)
      - Eggs of Syrphus Amereana, 1944 June 15 (Box 269:, Folder 1498)
      - Fly on "Beetree" Sawdust, 1944 June 15 (Box 269:, Folder 1499)
      - Cranefly, 1944 June 15 (Box 269:, Folder 1500)
      - Eggs of Spider, 1944 June 16 (Box 269:, Folder 1501)
      - W.M.T. Davis, Nellie, and Me, 1944 June 16 (Box 269:, Folder 1502)
      - Eye of Sphinx Moth, 1944 July 1 (Box 269:, Folder 1503)
      - Gold Bug, 1944 July 1 (Box 269:, Folder 1504)
      - Audubon Library, 1944 July 3 (Box 269:, Folder 1505-1506)
      - Horseshoe Crab, 1944 July 5 (Box 269:, Folder 1507)
      - Sweet Flag Leaves, 1944 July 7 (Box 269:, Folder 1508)
      - Wide-Leaved Grass, 1944 July 7 (Box 269:, Folder 1509)
      - Cecropia Asleep on Viburnum, 1944 July 7 (Box 269:, Folder 1510)
      - Robber Fly, 1944 July 8 (Box 269:, Folder 1511)
      - Halictus Bees, 1944 July 10 (Box 269:, Folder 1512-1513)
      - Eggs on Caterpillar, 1944 July 10 (Box 269:, Folder 1514)
      - Burs (Indian Lake), 1944 July 19 (Box 269:, Folder 1515)
      - Richard Gillman and Me, 1944 August 2 (Box 269:, Folder 1516)
      - Head of Horse Fly, 1944 August 2 (Box 269:, Folder 1517)
      - Ambush Bug, 1944 August 2 (Box 269:, Folder 1518)
      - Ichneumon (Silk Pouch from Caterpillar), 1944 August 2 (Box 269:, Folder 1519)
      - Galls, 1944 August 2 (Box 269:, Folder 1520-1521)
      - Water Arum and Seeds, 1944 August 2 (Box 269:, Folder 1522)
      - Lace bug, 1944 August 2 (Box 269:, Folder 1523)
      - Boy with Pet Sparrow, 1944 August 3 (Box 269:, Folder 1524-1525)
      - Dragonfly, 1944 August 6 (Box 269:, Folder 1526)
      - Tree Hopper Eggs in Froth, 1944 August 10 (Box 269:, Folder 1527)
      - Boy with Pet Sparrow, 1944 August 12 (Box 269:, Folder 1528)
      - Bagworm on Vikurmum, 1944 August 14 (Box 269:, Folder 1529)
      - Dragonfly, 1944 August 14 (Box 269:, Folder 1530)
      - Burdock Burs, 1944 August 15 (Box 269:, Folder 1531)
      - Closeup of Monarch, 1944 September 1 (Box 269:, Folder 1532)
      - Dragonfly, 1944 September 14 (Box 269:, Folder 1533)
      - Polistes on Small White Aster, 1944 September 1 (Box 269:, Folder 1534)
      - Red-Bodied Dragonfly, 1944 September 1 (Box 269:, Folder 1535)
      - Dragonfly, 1944 September 1 (Box 269:, Folder 1536)
      - Monarch, 1944 October 8 (Box 269:, Folder 1537)
      - Mantis Reared, 1944 October 9 (Box 269:, Folder 1538)
      - Mantis Face, 1944 October 9 (Box 269:, Folder 1539)
      - Mantis Specter Pose, 1944 October 9 (Box 269:, Folder 1540-1541)
      - Mantis on Zinnia, 1944 October 9 (Box 269:, Folder 1542)
      - Mantis Reared Behind Zinnia, 1944 October 10 (Box 269:, Folder 1543)
      - Mantis, 1944 October 10 (Box 269:, Folder 1544)